wpcurve.com 2017-04-21

# WP Curve privacy policy - WP Curve

WP CURVE PRIVACY POLICY

_Last Updated: September 3, 2013_

Lifetime Value LLC (“WP Curve” or “us” or “we”) developed this website (the “Website”) and the use of the Website is subject to your compliance with the privacy policy set forth below. We provide this Privacy Policy to ensure you understand your obligations and also explain how we use your personal information.

## Information we collect

WP Curve collects information when you subscribe to our Website, and use various other features and services we provide. In some cases, if you choose not to provide us with requested information, you may not be able to access all of the great content we provide.

**WP Curve Subscribers**

You can choose to subscribe to one of our free electronic newsletters or sign up for a member account. When you subscribe, we ask you to provide us with information such as your name, email address, city/state and other identifiable information. We keep this information on file to contact you with services and products related to the Website and to answer any questions or concerns you may have.

## How we use your information

Information about our customers is an important part of our business, and we are not in the business of selling it to others. We use the information you provide us to contact you about our products, features and services. WP Curve may also share information with third parties to assist in providing a more relevant and useful experience. The information collected on our Website in the aggregate enables us to better understand your use of the Website and to enhance your enjoyment.

It is possible that we may need to disclose the information you provide to our Website when we have a good faith belief that disclosure is necessary to (a) prevent illegal activity or assist government enforcement agencies; (b) to enforce other agreements and defend ourselves against allegations/claims; (c) to protect the rights, property or personal safety of WP Curve employees, users or others and/or (d) to protect the security or integrity of the Website. In those instances, the information is provided only for that limited purpose.

## Your information choices

If you visit our Website and volunteer personally identifiable information, you can always opt out of receiving content and review, modify, update, or delete such information by contacting alex@wpcurve.com. Please be aware that even after your request for a change is processed, WP Curve may, for a time, keep residual information about you in its backup and/or archival copies of its database.

## Your obligation as a user

As a user of our Website, you have certain obligations. Some are imposed by laws, and others have become commonplace in user friendly communities of like-minded members such as WP Curve:

You must, at all times, abide by the terms and conditions of our current Privacy Policy and Terms of Use Agreement. This includes respecting all intellectual property rights that may belong to third parties (such as trademarks or photographs).

You must not download or otherwise disseminate any information that may be deemed to be injurious, violent and offensive or which may otherwise violate the spirit of our Website.

Any violation of these guidelines may lead to the restriction, suspension or termination of your use of our Website.

## Your consent and changes

By using our Website, you consent to our use of information that is collected and submitted as described in this Privacy Policy. We reserve the right in our sole discretion to change, modify, add or delete the Privacy Policy at any time. We will provide notice of such changes only by posting the updated Privacy Policy on the Website and changing the “last updated” date listed above. The Privacy Policy applies exclusively to your access to, interaction with, and use of, the Website. We encourage you to review our Privacy Policy each time you visit the Website to see if it has been updated since your last visit.

## Security

We have security measures on our systems and work hard to secure your personal information from unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction. We periodically review our processing practices to guard against unauthorized access to our system. However, despite our efforts, we cannot ensure or completely guarantee a 100% secure environment. We restrict access to personal information to employees, contractors, and agents who need to know that information in order to process it for us, and who are subject to strict contractual confidentiality obligations and may be disciplined or terminated if they fail to meet these obligations.

## Waiver

WP CURVE ASSUMES NO RESPONSIBILITY OR LIABILITY WITH REGARD TO ANY THEFT, LOSS, ALTERATION OR MISUSE OF PERSONAL OR OTHER INFORMATION LAWFULLY PROVIDED BY WP CURVE TO THIRD PARTIES, OR WITH REGARD TO THE FAILURE OF ANY THIRD PARTY TO ABIDE BY THIS PRIVACY POLICY OR AGREEMENT BETWEEN THAT THIRD PARTY AND WP CURVE.

## How contact us

If you have questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, please email us at [alex@wpcurve.com](mailto:alex@wpcurve.com) or contact us at:

WP Curve  
PO Box 559  
Burleigh Heads,  
Queensland 4220  
Australia
